<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ITProTV Home Page on </title>
    <link>http://itpro.test:1380/</link>
    <description>Recent content in ITProTV Home Page on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="http://itpro.test:1380/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Accessibility | OfficeProTV</title>
      <link>http://itpro.test:1380/accessibility/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://itpro.test:1380/accessibility/</guid>
      <description> Accessibility In a mission to make ITProTV IT learning content available to all aspiring and existing Office professionals, our development team has worked to improve the accessibility of our website. OfficeProTV is WCAG 2.0 AA compliant. If you have any suggestions or concerns regarding our accessibility, please email support@officepro.tv.
New Features  New accessibilities controls for primary and audio players New accessibilities controls for live video player Restructured course library tabbing Restructured ratings Restructured downloads and added shortcut to download button Added tabbing shortcuts to content, to video player, and to top of navigation Labeled carousel buttons Added language to main html tag Added roles to navigation menu  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EULA | OfficeProTV</title>
      <link>http://itpro.test:1380/eula/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://itpro.test:1380/eula/</guid>
      <description>Terms and Conditions of Use 1. Introduction 1.1 Welcome to ITPro.TV. We hope that you enjoy your experience and thank you for subscribing. These Terms and Conditions of Use (the “Agreement”) govern your use of the Internet-based learning service provided through this site (“Service”). The Service consists of computing and information services and software, information, interactive forums, and other content provided by EdutainmentLIVE LLC. and its affiliates (“ITPro.TV”).
1.2 Your participation in the Service is conditioned upon your acceptance of this Agreement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Features | OfficeProTV</title>
      <link>http://itpro.test:1380/features/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://itpro.test:1380/features/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy | OfficeProTV</title>
      <link>http://itpro.test:1380/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://itpro.test:1380/privacy/</guid>
      <description>Privacy Policy What information do we collect? We collect information from you when you register on our site. When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously. What do we use your information for? Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>